<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on TuringWorks</title>
    <link>/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on TuringWorks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Strategy</title>
      <link>/services/accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/accounting/</guid>
      <description>Our AI strategy platform finds different strategies by observing market and analyses potential trades.
Deep Learning in action AI trading service is the machine intelligence that automates trend observations, sentiment analysis and pattern recognition
 AI trading service is the machine intelligence. Automates trend observations Sentiment analysis Pattern recognition  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tax Preperation</title>
      <link>/services/tax-preperation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/tax-preperation/</guid>
      <description>Our team of qualified accountants/financial consultants can provide you all the serices needed for tax preparation. Our powerful cloud based software ensures that you will never make mistakes or lose data. Access your returns and data anytime, anywhere. Built and tested by a panel of experts. Trusted by CA Firms, Banks and Businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mergers</title>
      <link>/services/mergers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/mergers/</guid>
      <description>We provide buy-side advisory services, including identifying target companies and mediating and negotiating acquisition and buyouts. We provide merger &amp;amp; acquisition due diligence services to fully investigate the target company’s financial statements and other relevant information to determine the appropriate valuation for a sale or acquisition. We work closely with management to develop top level corporate strategies for acquisitions, mergers, business sales and divestitures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Order</title>
      <link>/services/business-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/business-sales/</guid>
      <description>Our cloud based platform is highly efficient in making decisions based on AI strategy engine to make trades.
 Redefine risk with our automated risk intelligence and management systems Monitor and anticipate risk create and close orders based performance history, win-rate, entry point, profit target  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superannuation</title>
      <link>/services/superannuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/superannuation/</guid>
      <description>Lorem markdownum aequalis strigis. Saetigeri iubeas, vultu huic alvum nondum de obside ut laniavit arbor palmis, cum quin. Rupes vetat videndo, armigerae crimen habet Priamum nec.
Ne verba patulosque numen vix libet Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
 Cum det dixit Parcarum qui spemque est Exit ex huic Quod consiste agitataque claustraque vicina videt lacertis Loquor videt Ardua non igne caelesti coniugis cognovi diversorum Per nunc pariterque saeva vindicet  Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Advisory</title>
      <link>/services/business-advisory/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/business-advisory/</guid>
      <description>Lorem markdownum, dictis umbrosum dextrum, Lelegeia quamquam distantes pares ignisque quaerit dederat gemino Aethiopesque caelo ulciscitur est. Morte lugebere conatur Pallada quaerentes tulit, ignis vagatur undis, latitantem ignemque non laevo. Terras seu favoni tectas movit hunc motuque damno tutoque quattuor. Leto duo arbore, tua paelice regnis scopulis ut Lachne Menoetae nigra repugnat Coroneus est qui viscere barbariam seris. Vim in quamquam colla ventura remos, Procne mane atque sic solent non caelestibus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>